<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE errors PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD ErrorCorpus 0.1//EN" "errors.dtd">
<errors>

<!--
This is a collection of "real-world errors". Some of these errors can be detected
by LanguageTool, for the others rules need to be written yet.
-->
<category name="agreement">
	<s>Carsten Burghardt <replace by="has">have</replace> actually already implemented the folder selection.</s>
	<s>Ms. Zaheda resigned SUN, and currently Mr. Eric is the <replace by="person">people</replace> in charge of this.</s>
	<s>That project is my degree thesis, was <replace by="written">wrote</replace> 2 years ago and never touched ever since.</s>
	<s>Someone else <replace by="suggested">suggest</replace> to add this to linux/drivers/usb/storage/unusual_devs.h.</s>
	<s>...for developers <replace by="who">which</replace> are interested in issues related to KDE's file...</s>
	<s>I want you to read it and to give me a price <replace by="for">of</replace> <replace by="creating">create</replace> a Perl script that <replace by="fits">fit</replace> the requirements in that project, the perl script looks like e-commerce but it's very simple.</s>
	<s>The report must also discuss the problems faced while doing the assignment, how the problems were <replace by="overcome">overcame</replace>, and the lessons learned.</s>
	<s>The Web site also <replace by="contains">contain</replace> fields for the user to enter their details: ...</s>
	<s>Or did that rule <replace by="change">changed</replace> while I was on vacation?</s>
	<s>Does each version of MySql <replace by="have">has</replace> binary AND src version for installation?</s>
	<s>And what about the ones who <replace by="don't">doesn't</replace> have wireless?</s>
	<s>This is a set of changes that is well <replace by="tested">test</replace> by myself and others.</s>
	<s>Anything about UPB <replace by="has">was</replace> already <replace by="been written">wrote</replace>.</s>
	<s>JFYI, KMail now <replace by="supports">support</replace> S/MIME through a plugin.</s>
	<s><replace by="Following">Follow</replace> Eike's advice, now I am <replace by="joining">join</replace> the maillist.</s>
	<s>If you mirror kde-www on kdemirror.de, you <replace by="only have to">has only to</replace> change your local config.php</s>
	<s>...which is right in many <replace by="ways">way</replace>,...</s>
	<s>I now have <replace by="understood">understand</replace> that it is the IMAP-server I'm using.</s>
	<s>I might <replace by="forget">forgot</replace> to send it then.</s>
	<s>Where can I <replace by="find">found</replace> a fix?</s>
	<s type="Email subject">Re: Can't <replace by="prevent">Preventing</replace> exploitation with rebasing</s>
	<s><replace by="Did">Does</replace> the problem <remove>has</remove> <replace by="appear">appeared</replace> after an update of KDE or not?</s>
	<s>You will <replace by="lose">lost</replace> all your changes!</s>
	<s>I have not <replace by="said">say</replace> that is a MySpell problem I would like only to signal it ...</s>
	<s>For maximum ability to nail spambots, consider using a cgi directory that is not <replace by="named">names</replace> "cgi-bin".</s>
	<s>Doing so we have <replace by="created">create</replace> a my.cnf in mysql datadir containing:</s>
	<s type="Bug report summary">Click on a folder and then move the mouse may <replace by="select">selects</replace> wrong folder</s>
	<s>Display a column in the list of folders which <replace by="shows">show</replace> the number of unread messages per folder.</s>
	<s>When using javascript menus, the pop-up menus are <replace by="shown">showed</replace> at the back...</s>
	<s>The patch has only <replace by="been">be</replace> applied to KOffice.</s>
	<s>If it <replace by="isn't">doesn't be</replace> stable/mature enough before 3.1 final, I will....</s>
	<s>...but Dirk <replace by="told">tell</replace> me to go ahead ;)</s>
	<s>I fixed buglist.cgi and the show_activity.cgi and <replace by="sent">send</replace> in the patch.</s>
	<s>Well, as long as there is no link to both of these, <replace by="it">I</replace> doesn't affect the problem we wanted to address.</s>
	<s>...since it was noticed that Sebastian also had <replace by="made">make</replace> a suggestion about it.</s>
	<s>Has anyone <replace by="considered">considering</replace> writing interface test suites...</s>
	<s>I <replace by="produce">produces</replace> all the arguments...</s>
	<s>We need to <replace by="find">found</replace> a common layer...</s>
	<s><replace by="I">I'm</replace> do not run a mix of OS...</s>
	<s>I do not run a mix of OS and it <replace by="is">are</replace> a long time ago...</s>
	<s>Why <replace by="do">does</replace> I still install a not used eventFilter ;)</s>
	<s>That <replace by="wasn't">doesn't was</replace> my intention.</s>
	<s>Have no probs with your stuff, but why <replace by="do">does</replace> we need an undock button?</s>
	<s>I am sure others <replace by="have">has</replace> a list as long as mine.</s>
	<s>...but I hope in a few <replace by="years">year</replace> it will...</s>
	<s>...which does not <replace by="have">has</replace> 50% threshold.</s>
	<s>It is updated every few <replace by="days">day</replace>.</s>
	<s>What would <replace by="happen">happend</replace>, if someone writes...</s>
	<s>Why <replace by="is">does</replace> kmail HEAD afraid of using kdelibs HEAD?</s>
	<s>The emails of this form should <replace by="go">goes</replace> to this email address: ...</s>
	<s>We would be glad if this little helper would be able to help other <replace by="developers">developer</replace>.</s>
	<s>You can <replace by="find">found</replace> it on my web page.</s>
	<s>Did you maybe <replace by="miss">missed</replace> the kconf_update run that updates the signature config?</s>
	<s>No, the indexes should be <replace by="built">build</replace> automatically.</s>
	<s>I <replace by="improved">improves</replace> it a bit...</s>
	<s>3.0.4 is mostly <replace by="known">know</replace> for miscompiling aRts, and the fix was too large to merge.</s>
	<s>IIRC you told me a long time ago GnuPG 1.0.7 was to be <replace by="released">release</replace> the "next weekend".</s>
	<s>I had a look into this and the dialog didn't <replace by="get">got</replace> deleted.</s>
	<s>Does somebody <replace by="know">knows</replace> more?</s>
	<s>I solved this by <replace by="moving">move</replace> all folders to IMAP, which was a task for months.</s>
	<s>I solved this by moving all folders to IMAP, which was a task for <replace by="months">month</replace>.</s>
	<s>I always get these <replace by="errors">error</replace>.</s>
	<s>It <replace by="does">do</replace> <replace by="have">has</replace> some bugs though.</s>
	<s>In chap. 7, it <replace by="discusses">discussing</replace> using signals and slots to create a little xml parser, which then displays a tree list view.</s>
</category>

<category name="missing words">
	<s>It <insert>will</insert> reach 1.0 soon.</s>
	<s>I <insert>am</insert> just surprised though that Opera developers are of such high opinion about their Opera browser.</s>
	<s>The result of the work on NPTL, the new thread implementation, can <insert>be</insert> checked out.</s>
	<s>The language patch has <insert>been</insert> added to http://www.danielnaber.de/perlfectsearch/.</s>
	<s>I'll definitely step by at the KDE booth, maybe we can <insert>make</insert> arrangements there.</s>
	<s>I think<remove>,</remove> it's ready <insert>to</insert> replace cvs2pack.</s>
	<s>So please if the admin did not add <insert>an</insert> image, let the script <remove>to</remove> take this image automatically.</s>
	<s>If they are already up to date, then I <insert>thought</insert> it is enough to replace the date and the version to acknowledge that they have been verified.</s>
	<s>That dump can then <insert>be</insert> used to figure out just what went wrong.</s>
	<s>That <insert>is</insert> why we will add a function to the token definitions.</s>
	<s>Wouldn't you <insert>go</insert> mad if I fork your program, modifiy it and come up to all others with it to trash your original program out of kde without one single personal email?</s>
	<s>...we should be able to let this structure live on for <insert>a</insert> year.</s>
	<s>I don't <insert>think</insert> KDE eV yet owns any domain names.</s>
	<s>So, could we have at least the option of threading just by subject and ignoring <insert>???</insert> completely.</s>
	<s>These user unfriendly message boxes have <insert>been</insert> the reason to leave windows95 seven years ago ;-)</s>
	<s>Being annoyed by today's debian-security OFF TOPIC ranting, I noticed my wish for <insert>this</insert> feature, ...</s>
	<s>For local files with a known <insert>???</insert>, simply create a KFileItem and pass it to the other constructor.</s>
	<s>...test if more <insert>or</insert> less everything works...</s>
	<s>In KDE 2.2.0 and KDE 2.2.1 we <insert>had</insert> a bug that caused KMail...</s>
	<s>Of <insert>course</insert> this isn't a general solution.</s>
	<s>...but I hope in <insert>a</insert> few <replace by="years">year</replace> it will...</s>
	<s>I volunteer to create <insert>a</insert> testcase then.</s>
	<s>Kyoto was <insert>the</insert> oldest capital city in Japan.</s>
</category>

<category name="extra words">
	<s>I discussed the contest with Lukas Tinkl so here is the very latest revision of the <remove>much</remove> famous (!) Koffice Icon Contest.</s>
	<s>Someone <remove>suggested</remove> said that it worked for him after he updated to Kernel 2.4.20.</s>
	<s>Selecting <remove>a</remove> folders to be synchronized, ...</s>
	<s>But, probably, it will be <remove>more</remove> better to set the default language of Automatic Detection by "KGlobal::locale()->languageList()[0]".</s>
	<s>As I said, we only have <remove>a</remove> very few weeks left and have to march towards that date very efficiently.</s>
	<s>Actually, the more I think about it, I like Daniel's proposal <replace by="">the</replace> best.</s>
	<s>I must <remove>to</remove> try it.</s>
	<s>I'm hoping that bugzilla.kde.org <remove>that</remove> <remove>it</remove> will be found to be flexible enough...</s>
	<s>There is <remove>a</remove> <replace by="some">small</replace> research done on what effects has the computer on education.</s>
	<s>We can always slip it by <remove>for</remove> 2-3 weeks by adding another release candidate</s>
	<s>Kyoto was the <remove>most</remove> oldest capital city in Japan.</s>
	<s>You can find it among <remove>with</remove> my patches on my web page.</s>
	<s>I <remove>will</remove> wrote to an e-mail you told me.</s>
	<s>This will be <remove>a</remove> much work.</s>
	<s>If you <remove>are</remove> use SMTP to send your messages, ...</s>
	<s>You must <remove>to</remove> fill the Document Info.</s>
	<s>Can somebody remember how the fix <remove>have</remove> worked?</s>
</category>

<category name="wrong word">
	<s>Sorry, but the backtrace is <replace by="completely">complete</replace> useless.</s>
	<s>With the <replace by="current">currently</replace> system load I don't think that will be successful.</s>
	<!-- "is _ most powerful" mit _ = anything except the|a: -->
	<s>In which case is Ruby <replace by="more">most</replace> powerful than Python?</s>
	<s>The person that claims for the authory of the TWO "PhpNuke SQL Injection" has discovered them at the same time <replace by="as">than</replace> me and exploits them _exactly_ the same way.</s>
	<s>...well it's <replace by="easier">easy</replace> now than it was before...</s>
	<s>The patch has only been applied <replace by="to">for</replace> KOffice.</s>
	<s>Sorry, I have to correct <replace by="myself">me</replace>.</s>
	<s>Only during the <replace by="weekend">week end</replace> I ...</s>
	<s>...since it was noticed that Sebastian also had made <replace by="a">an</replace> suggestion about it.</s>
	<s>I guess this isn't easily <replace by="possible">possibly</replace>.</s>
	<s>Surely not before KDE 3.1 (think of translations etc.), <replace by="right">or</replace>?!?</s>
	<s>I already did that, but it does not work, <replace by="either">too</replace>.</s>
	<s>I changed one behaviour with my original commit, which is not consistent with EXCEL <replace by="either">too</replace>.</s>
	<s>This doesn't belong here, <replace by="either">too</replace>.</s>
	<s>KDE League <replace by="does not have">has not</replace> enough man power <replace by="either">too</replace> and cannot do as much as could be possible.</s>
	<s>Are you planning to add non-English documentation <replace by="too">either</replace>?</s>
	<s>I'll think a bit more <replace by="about">on</replace> this and ...</s>
</category>

<category name="confusion of similar words">
	<s>Thanks for <replace by="your">you</replace> interest in our service.</s>
	<s>It's a bit more <replace by="than">then</replace> 15 min. for me.</s>
	<!-- TODO?: no 'than' at the beginning of a sentence?: -->
	<s><replace by="Then">Than</replace> my old email is nonsense.</s>
	<s>I volunteer to create a testcase <replace by="then">than</replace>.</s>
	<s>It is also harder to maintain stability in the code base with small changes that just fix the bugs <replace by="than">then</replace> to reorganise often.</s>
	<s>It's less controversial <replace by="than">then</replace> one would think :)</s>
	<s>We show that our system achieves state of the art performance in text chunking with less computational cost <replace by="than">then</replace> previous systems.</s>
	<s>Starting over just so we can integrate GNOME and KDE apps fully is a waste of time and more work <replace by="than">then</replace> just perfecting the apps we have.</s>
	<s>If you click on the same column more <replace by="than">then</replace> once, ...</s>
	<s>I am not wiser <replace by="than">that</replace> you but I try to listen to others when it becomes...</s>
	<s>I'd rather keep all the syntax highlighters in one file until it gets <replace by="too">to</replace> big.</s>
	<s>Ok, I wrote this to you, that you don't have to do <replace by="too">to</replace> much research for your KDE-CVS digest...</s>
	<s>This is not <replace by="too">to</replace> close at the Linuxtag, so that there are not two events which have to be organized at the same time and it doesn't overlap <replace by="too">to</replace> much with school holidays.</s>
	<s>This will perform a commit whenever the cache gets <replace by="too">to</replace> full.</s>
	<s>...but now it's getting <replace by="too">to</replace> complicated and time-consuming for me.</s>
	<s>Ideally we should have one database, not <replace by="two">too</replace>.</s>
	<s>Someone has <replace by="to">too</replace> keep it up to date.</s>
	<s>Indexing the whole directory would take <replace by="too">to</replace> long</s>
	<s>The identity you are using <replace by="to">the</replace> write the current message needs to...</s>
	<s>...but also easily uses all available file handlers (on Linux systems) if you have <replace by="too">to</replace> many folders.</s>
	<s>If the application + FS interaction leads to contention, then you have <replace by="two">to</replace> choices to optimize:...</s>
	<s>Note: the links in this display <replace by="do">to</replace> not work yet.</s>
	<s>Unhide can be triggered by moving <replace by="the">to</replace> mouse to a corner.</s>
	<s>I think <replace by="you're">your</replace> confused.</s>
	<s>I want to see <replace by="your">you</replace> printer.</s>
	<s>Are you in a position where <replace by="your">you</replace> company will let you contribute patches...</s>
	<s>Thanks again for your help and good luck for <replace by="your">you</replace> KDE Edu submission.</s>
	<s>The biggest user benefit in this is that <replace by="your">you</replace> local disk usage is almost zero.</s>
	<s>Maybe Ingo should just have reverted <replace by="your">you</replace> damned dump.</s>
	<s>Where's <replace by="your">you</replace> point?</s>
	<s>You should ask <replace by="your">you</replace> admin.</s>
	<s>Thanks again <replace by="for">fore</replace> your help and good luck for your KDE Edu submission.</s>
	<s>I work for a publishing house and <replace by="we">were</replace> are in the process of conceptualizing various books on Linux.</s>
	<s><replace by="If">Of</replace> you disable this option, ...</s>
	<s>The next test will tell us <replace by="if">it</replace> the usb &lt;-&gt; scsi emulation is working correctly, run this on the console.</s>
	<s><replace by="If">Is</replace> our licenses are compatible, would you care to take over integrating a new thesaurus into OOo as well?</s>
	<s>You may CC me if you <replace by="think">thing</replace> you must...</s>
	<s>So I <replace by="think">thing</replace> we will...</s>
	<s>Aethera <replace by="used">use</replace> to use KParts.</s>
	<s>Please don't <replace by="use">us</replace> dispose!</s>
	<s>But I think <replace by="it's">it</replace> serious:...</s>
	<s>If the cafeteria is open (which <replace by="it">is</replace> wasn't the last day at GUADEC 3).</s>
	<s>The Kopete team has decided <replace by="it's">its</replace> time we should move to kdenetwork if we want to be included in KDE 3.2.</s>
	<s>It is more correct to say that the AEGYPTEN branch has landed *on* <replace by="its">it's</replace> HEAD ;-)</s>
	<s><replace by="Of">Off</replace> course not.</s>
	<s>KHTML is just the only part of KDE I know <replace by="of">off</replace> that uses automasking.</s>
	<s>... - though there is not much you can <replace by="buy">by</replace> for $0.02 let alone 0.02 euro ;-)</s>
	<s>$1k would not be enough to <replace by="buy">by</replace> the beer for the people who develop The GIMP.</s>
	<s>You can discuss <replace by="the">then</replace> warnings and determine if any of them are valid.</s>
	<s>We can make sure it works and <replace by="then">the</replace> just have to change the link.</s>
	<s>Thanks for the <replace by="response">responds</replace>.</s>
	<s>Or <replace by="was">way</replace> that a very recent change in Qt?</s>
	<s>...<replace by="therefore">there for</replace> we should try to fix...</s>
	<s>Or we just <replace by="throw">through</replace> away all bugs and start from scratch :-)</s>
	<s>I have <replace by="now">no</replace> introduced a yPosition() function...</s>
	<s>We think it helps finding bottlenecks and so <replace by="on">one</replace>.</s>
	<s>I'm <replace by="not">nut</replace> sure... ;-)</s>
	<s>Please <replace by="note">not</replace> that saying "Open Source" does not mean very much.</s>
	<s><replace by="Add">At</replace> to that retarded corporate intranets with Windows DNS and mail servers.</s>
	<s>Ah, I <replace by="knew">new</replace> you would say that.</s>
	<s>But be warned that caching and downloading <replace by="are">a</replace> two completely different things.</s>
	<s>I can be pretty <replace by="dumb">dump</replace> when it comes to such things...</s>
	<s>Your best <replace by="chance">change</replace> to meet some of them...</s>
	<s><replace by="Who">How</replace> else has to be involved in this process?</s>
	<s>But even if it's looking fine, <replace by="there">the</replace> is the problem that for lots of calls you...</s>
	<s>I <replace by="thought">though</replace>...</s>
	<s>I <replace by="am">a</replace> not wiser than you but I try to listen to others when it becomes...</s>
	<s>Jeremy Hylton noticed that in ceval that <replace by="there">their</replace> is a test of whether...</s>
	<s>Unfortunately <replace by="there">their</replace> are some problems with your patch:</s>
	<s>There are two things I know about branches: <replace by="they">the</replace> always introduce bugs and inconsistencies.</s>
	<s>I guess simply turning this <replace by="off">of</replace> isn't easily possible.</s>
	<s>I have been out with the <replace by="flu">flew</replace> for the past 3 days.</s>
	<s>You could put the antenna of your radio to this applet and <replace by="hear">here</replace> the sound...</s>
	<s>The initial data needs to be under <replace by="an">and</replace> Open Source lincense.</s>
	<s>For example, it is highly unlikely <replace by="that">than</replace> any system will learn human dialogue performance from dialogue transcripts...</s>
	<s>No surprise, since the trash folder is the only <replace by="one">on</replace> for me that automatically expires.</s>
	<s>Searching is really simple: Type in one or more words into <replace by="the">to</replace> search field and click "Search" (or press Return).</s>
	<s>Searching is really simple: Type in one <replace by="or">ore</replace> more words...</s>
	<s>The initial OOo thesaurus implementation was a real hack job basically thrown together by me to fill a <replace by="hole">whole</replace> and get myself up to speed with how lingucomponents interact with OOo and what it was like to write cross-platform code using the SAL abstraction layer.</s>
	<s>Now, this is <replace by="where">were</replace> my ignorance sets in.</s>
	<s>It is nice <replace by="to">the</replace> read this.</s>
	<s>You see everything at <replace by="once">one</replace> without clicking in the list.</s>
	<s>I believe you <replace by="have">half</replace> to turn on ExecCGI for the public_html dir.</s>
	<s>As you probably know, my native language <replace by="is">in</replace> Russian, plus I talk some other Cyrillic-based languages.</s>
	<s>You can get my photo <replace by="here">hear</replace>: ...</s>
	<s>If the last word <replace by="is">in</replace> incorrect, it gets underlined.</s>
	<s>We really <replace by="were">where</replace> popular...</s>
	<s>I think in <replace by="case">cause</replace> coolo didn't do it already we can include...</s>
	<s>Yes it is, to a certain <replace by="extent">extend</replace>.</s>
	<s>Going in Settings/SpellChecker and change the language <replace by="there">their</replace> is not so cool ;)</s>
	<s>Of <replace by="course">cause</replace> there is much more to see in the respective regions.</s>
	<s>This point is <replace by="moot">mood</replace> as there is no active/passive membership status.</s>
	<s><replace by="Then">The</replace> it won't compile...</s>
	<s>If you don't <replace by="activate">active</replace> the OpenPGP plugin then KMail will use the built-in inline OpenPGP by default.</s>
</category>

<category name="word order">
	<s>Why should Sebastian waste his time for changing that "details" on his design if we <replace by="cannot even">not even can</replace> agree that the left side menu will make it for the content pages?</s>
	<s>...and btw., <replace by="do you think">think you</replace> the www/kde-ev should move to...</s>
	<s>I can give you <replace by="a more detailed">more a detailed</replace> description of what's necessary.</s>
	<s><replace by="Can someone">Does someone can</replace> reproduce what I described before?</s>
</category>

<category name="comma">
	<s>Please select a template<remove>,</remove> that matches the csv file.</s>
	<s>I don't think<remove>,</remove> this is the job of the KDE League reps.</s>
	<s>Thanks to everyones reponses on this<insert>,</insert> really useful to know.</s>
</category>

<category name="whitespace">
	<s>In which case is Ruby more powerful than Python<remove> </remove>?</s>
</category>

<!-- Uncategorized errors
The correction is in brackets, "[]" = word needs to be removed to correct the sentence

English:
		But may be I miss understand[misunderstand] you and...
		Does[Do] I miss something?
		I did want[what] you said but still errors:
		I can manually delete the file[files] that are not able to be deleted by the application.
		Can any guru help me to[] find the reason?
		where we should store the interfaces of other the[word order] core extension points.
		Do[Did] you tried browse[try to browse] the ui with lynx?
		I copied the war file to /root/ but I [am] getting errors.
		Very thanks for your help.
		I believe the CLucene developers are more focused on providing a indexing/searching library that other[s?] can build an application with
		My be[Maybe] you all would found it interesting to talk with each other, just for conversation.
		May be -> maybe?
		Here is a list of things that need to be done so that another language can use of[] OpenThesaurus to create their own thesaurus:
		Are not there[word order] any disadvanteges in the area of getting good page scores?
		He is in[on?] vaction this week.
		No, in the moment[currently] not.
		There always might be results,[no comma] which are not the closest,[no comma?] but fit much better. 
		Regarding nutch, I [am] especially interested in using it as a framework...
		So something must of[have] happened to grow HEAD a lot!
		...and that [it] make[s] no sense to maintain 2 implementation[s] in one project.
		It is difficult to speeding[speed] this process more up [word order].
		...data comes throw[through] the network...
		It can [be] defined like that.
		Re: DOT SThere is a know[known] bug in Netscape Navigator version 4.0.xerver again down [word order: down again]?
		I have [a] problem with Nutch-04 ver. 
		Make it sense to not use the getDetail method and write a getUrl() instead?
		Working with brunches is a pain, I [am] busy enough to keep in sync with cvs head.
		lost[loss?] of data in case temp filder is full 
		Note that this only work[works] for small sites
		What we need is a very simple peace[piece] of software which we can run...
		...because of there[their] content an[and] so one[on],
		... since the internal encoding used by Aspell never actually has to [be] visible outside of Aspell since all input can be in UTF-8...
		If Aspell every[ever] supports these languages ...
		...the implementation is just confusing me and my be other people too
		It does [sound] like file i/o is now your bottleneck.
		Yes, I do you[use] the  same analyzer for indexing and searching.
		In this case Lucene would run [out] of memory too, ...
		How best is it to segment your indices? (???)
		Just split thinks[things] and setup a huge query farm that hopefully can
		   handle the load?
		.Can any one point me to [the] right direction...
		When I look ate[at] the code it seems...
		But does[is] the order be[] the same for all documents.[?]
		Does somebody has[have] an idea how to solve this problem?
		In case you wish to make an[] pressure that someone fix[es] this...
		this is not the same thing than[as]...
		If you[] a developer feels like reviewing...
		May[Maybe] we can do some test scripts...
		Sounds that interesting? [Does...]
		Them[Then] check if there...
		I new[knew] none related issues now
		Should be[we] add a...
		However I person[personally] think that the nutch....
		Again, this is just a request -- but it[if] you guys think it's not going to be widely used feel free to ignore it.
		...but he did not many[make] any changes.
		I'm vary[very] happy to announce that we join...
		I[If] the data changes, one server will know the change. 
		I think not, ...[I don't think so]
		Thank you, I supposed this, [??? "ich habe das schon vermutet..."]
		As a next step I wanted to have an additional group that allowed my[me] to analyze the revenue...
		Bit[But] myspell standard does not handle this correctly
		..., e.g. it support[s] phrase searches...
		If you a[are] pretty sure of the quality of the query,...
		Also does clucene lib is reliable[word order, ...]?
		The contribution to the community by other people, who write documentations or do sometimes mundane tasks, where only investigated marginally my[by] researchers. 
		Does this really happen always you select another folder? [???]
		Porting this to a new a new["a new" doppelt] layer would be...
 		If you can [...] your app with 1.9...
	 	I tried it with out[without] the rewite but that didn't help.
		... a key component in supporting development for OS X and  will be come[become] even more so as the migration to Intel progresses.
		I think the solution Mark has suggested does solves[solve] the problem in an acceptable way.
		It's actually gonna be a little better than the solution the customer is[] has right now.
		What I need to do is give the user the possibility to search for a phrase that starts at the and[end] of a page.
		other then[than]
		One problem is that you often don't [know] where a sentence starts and ends.
 		If you don't want the tools to appear on the KDE Control Center of[or] you just don't want to bother with libpythonize...
		For the above kind of check one might like to change this since other wise[otherwise] it will be somewhat arbitray which of color or colour is encounterd first.
		...and continue until the last one without out[] being interrupted by...
		...that won't happen also[either].
		This allows is[us] to really just have one place where we have to write our code..
 		I'll leave it us[up] to you to decide whether to include this...
  		The talk will given[give] an overview about what the new version of the office suite is capable of.
		I know how to to[do] this, ...

		see http://esl.about.com/library/grammar/blgr_adverbs.htm and otherd
		...and it uses Lucene for all it's[its] searching.
		It's really Alpha quality so you don't will[won't] see a big announcement splash for it.
		There is a know[known] bug in Netscape Navigator version 4.0.x
		This has been fixes[fixed] some time ago...
		It should index ad[and] search the Arabic/English text
		...followed by and[any] word that is not "and" or "to".
		The NutchBeans looks to see if your[you're] using multiple search servers...
		...and it has meet[met] each of these challenges wonderfully.  
		OOo scripting and addon production is just an other[another] way...
		...a[the] biggest house...
		a lot vs. allot
		flu <-> flew + andere homophone (mal im web nach einer Liste suchen)
		tree [three] months
		That's no[not] correct
		When I first me[met] my future wife...
		In + der = Inder:
			alle Tippfehler, die durch weglassen von Leerzeichen entsehen können
			ermitteln (2 Wörter zusammenziehen + Lisa, wenn bekannt -> mögl. Fehler)
		a/the <adj> walks: always wrong?
		be come -> become
			
German:
		Zuletzt waren die Reserven vor einem Jahre[Jahr] nach dem Durchzug des Hurrikans "Ivan" angezapft worden.
		Auf zwei Prozessoren ist es teilweise langsame[langsamer] als auf einem einzelnen.
		fragen haben -> Fragen haben
		Sein Ziel, 2004 ein operatives Ergebnis von 2,5 Milliarden Euro zu erreichen, ist nicht mehr [zu] schaffen.
		In welchen[welchem] Heft?
		Ein[Eine] eindeutige Antwort hierauf ist zur Zeit nicht zu bekommen.
		Dieser mit 15.000 Dollar dotierter[dotierte] Preis gehört zu den renommiertesten Auszeichnungen für Autoren und Schriftstellern[Schriftsteller] in den Vereinigten Staaten.
		Die beide[beiden] Admins aus Peking haben in der Mailingliste der chinesischen Admins berichtet,...
		Der Internet-Portalbetreiber Lycos Europe offeriert inzwischen einen eigenen E-Mail-Dienst mit einem Speichervolumen von ebenfalls einem Gigabyte an[].
		Erst gestern berichtete der "Kölner Stadt-Anzeiger" [er] habe einen Schlaganfall erlitten. 
		Manchmal wünschen[wünsche] ich mir, bei einer seit kurzem...
		Ich danke[denke] das ist es.
		Ich hoffe, dass der neuen[neue] Server deutlich...
		..senken wollte, müssen[müsste] man etwa 10 Mrd...
		Es[?] bekomme ich die eigentliche VE-Runtime nicht mehr rein!
		Der[Die] weltweite Stärkung der erneuerbaren Energien ist beschlossene Sache.
		Aus dem Grunde konnte er die Kraft entwickeln so lange am Ball zu bleiben und bei der Entwicklung trotz Rckschläge[n] nicht aufzuhören.
		Unterdessen [...] sich Pläne des Bundesfinanzministeriums, das Tanken in anderen EU-Ländern...
		Ich bin mir ziemlich sich[sicher] dass es nicht möglich sein wird VBA-Makros zu importieren.
		Analog zum Empfinden der Ostdeutschen hat sich [nach] Ansicht des Wissenschaftlers heute...
		...bist du eigentlich auf der sichere[sicheren] Seite.
		schwer von begriff[Begriff] sein
		Eine Besonderheit bei der Transliteration stellt das Serbische da[dar], da es offiziell...
		Bei einem ökonomischen[�umenisch] Gottesdienst
		...aber denn[dann]...
		...innerhalb von 20 Jahre[Jahren] verdoppeln.
		Die widriger[widrigen] Umstände, die die Familie in Ihrem Aufruf an die Gäste anspricht...
		So wie es aussieht, kappt[klappt] das im Moment nicht. 
		Das mit der Indexierung kann ich noch ein[] etwas ausführlicher beschreiben...
		Im laufe[Laufe?] des Tages...
		In Etwa[etwa]...
		im Zaun[Zaum] halten (??)
		Dann werden wir uns ja da Treffen[treffen]...
		Bei der suche[Suche] nach Jobs...
		Globalisierungs- Kritiker feiern Kindergeburtstag [kein Leerz. hinter dem "-"]
		beim/am/dem/das erhitzen [immer groß nach diesen Wörtern?!]
		Damit will der[das] Gespann allen Interessierten einen ersten...
		Wieso [Wie so] oft/häufig...
		Das Parallelprojekt Volcano ist dem[] hauptsächlich dem Re-Design von Firebird gewidmet.
		Je nach Vorlieben kann der Fahrer Radio, Klimaanlage, Navigation oder Telefon direkt am Gerät, ber Schalter am Multifunktionslenkrad oder mit Hilfe des weiterentwickelte[weiterentwickelten] Command-Systems steuern. 
		Mehr als drei Millionen Haushalt[Haushalte] in Deutschland...
		Auch für Familien seien die Anreize zur Erwerbsaufnahme durch[] wegen der Kinderzuschläge beim Arbeitslosengeld II gering.
		Lediglich in eigen[einigen] Großstädten ist durch sogenannte City-Tarife noch ein Sparpotential von bis zu 50 Prozent möglich.
		..sicher ber alle Unzuverlässigkeiten hinwegtrösten zu lasen[lassen].
		nicht zerlegtest [zerlegtes] Kompositum
		Gestern hatte Bundessozialministerin Schmidt(SPD)[Leerz. vor der Klammer] bestätigt...
		...jedoch aber...[Verdoppelung]
		...damit ich [einen] Blick drauf werfe.
		die Bereitstellung ausreichender Teilnehmer- Informationen für Rückwärts-Auskünfte. [kein Leerzeichen nach "Teilnehmer-"]
		Wahlberechtigt zur Bundestagswahl sind alle Deutschen, die am Wahltag des[das] 18. Lebensjahr vollendet haben, seit mindestens drei Monaten in Deutschland leben...
		Der Hauptindex kann die Ergebnissen[Ergebnisse] der Indizierung anschließend sofort nutzen.
		Die Liste aus dem Netz enthält keine Eigenname[n], oder?
		Fr die Besetzung der Stellen suchen wir gleichmaßen[gleichermaßen?] Frauen und Männer.
		Linux+ ist ein europäsches Magazin ber Linux, dass[das] seit 1997 vom Verlag Software Wydawnictwo herausgegeben wird.
		Wie kriege ich dein[deine] Dokumentation?
		Sie werden von der reichen Auswahl slowenischer Spitzenweinen[Spitzenweine] begeistert.
		Wenn ihr das brauche[brauchen] könnt...
		Richard Hilmer von Infratest hatte daraufhin erklärt, der Wahlausgang könne dich[doch] noch knapper werden als bislang erwartet. 
		Dieses sehr ausgefallende[ausgefallene] Einfamilienhaus hat ein Satteldach....
		Tags zuvor hatte Wahlkampf-Manager Bodo Ramelow allerdings gegenüber SPIEGEL ONLINE . [verb fehlt]
		Ich werde Sie auf dem laufenden[Laufenden] halten.
		in aller kürze[Krze]
		wieder[wider] Erwarten
		...durch das verweilen[Verweilen] des Mauszeigers...
		aus versehen[Versehen]
		mal Bescheide[Bescheid] sagen/geben
		Für dieses Jahr wurde die Prognose von 0,7 auf 0,8 Prozent. [Verb fehlt]
			
		bereit bestehende -> bereits bestehende
		Das[Dass] solche ��rungen Wahlen beeinflussen k�nen...
		Die Enterprise-Version unterstützt Mehrprozessor Systemen[Systeme].
		Die Enterprise-Version unterstützt Mehrprozessorsystemen[..systeme].
		"sie Suche" -> die Suche
			
		===== similar words:
		Vortag Vortrag
		===== similar words (some not errors if any compound is accepted):
		Schneelocke Schneeflocke
		Schaufelstern Schaufenstern
		Unterschiede Unterscheide (okay am Satzanfang)
		stellt ... da -> stellt ... dar
		Bindestrick -> ..strich
		Quallenangabe -> Quellenangabe
		Rückganz -> Rückgang

		OTHER:
		Vergleichs vs Vergleiches (einheitlich pro dokument)
		-beachten, beobachten: brauchen Akkusativ!?
			"wegen": Gen. oder Dativ
			sehen: Akk
			auf: Dativ

Hungarian:  fen akad fen + Verb -> error
-->
</errors>
